I was in community college
when I first crossed
paths with that buzzkill
of a man I call my husband.
It turned out he went to one of
the ritzier colleges in the area.
My friends at the time thought he
was dreamy and fawned over the guy.
The fact that I was the girl on his
arm made me feel a bit superior.
Then we had a kid.
I get it because it's three
times faster. The picture.
Oh come on. Hayato.
At least say hi.
Hi mom.
It's not that my husband's a bad person.
He's not even a heavy.
drinker.
And he might not bring home a big
paycheck, but he's a damn hard worker.
Even
so, I fell into a marriage
without ever knowing love.
So he's finally home.
All I ever hear
is where's dinner, make me
a bath, I'm going to bed.
Jeez, what a bore.
I'm home.
Where's dinner?
Oh, hey, you're finally home.
I didn't even hear you open the door.
Sorry, I was too busy to cook.
That'll have to do.
But your favorite's on the table.
I bet he's pissed.
Let's see if he's man enough
to do something about it.
Who am I kidding?
You're gonna sit there stuffing your
face in silence like you always do.
Radio.
Good evening.
This is Mariah Radio.
Kai Howard here, your neighborhood
purveyor of good lives.
Hey, what you doing over there?
How is everyone on this fine night?
Great, I hope.
Allow me to ease you
into a mellow journey.
We found his house about 15
minutes away from Mariah Station.
It was in a part of town known
for its views and villas.
Actually, it was his former house,
where he lived as Yoshikage Kira.
Now he has a new face, a new job,
a new place to call home, and
probably even a new family.
It's obvious that he's
never turning up here again,
but just the same, we still
have to search the place.
If we're going to find any clues as
to where this new man ran off to,
we're going to find them
right here in this house.
Huh given how much that kid looks
like our guy this must be his album
Yoshikage Kira he was born in Mariah
on January 30th 1966 he's nearly two
meters tall he weighs 65 kilograms
and his blood type is A he was born
to older parents when he was 21 his
father Yoshihiro fell ill and died
Seems his mother died soon after.
Graduated in 1988 with
a degree in literature.
Same year, he starts at Kameyu in S-City,
and in 1993 transfers to the Mariah branch.
He has no previous criminal record,
has never married, has no
close friends or lover.
He's never even had a surgery.
And we can't find him with fingerprints,
dental records, or surgical scars.
So what you're trying to say
is we've reached a dead end.
Check it out.
The trophies and plaques
they all say third
place so he certainly
wasn't a star athlete.
Nothing speaks to his
talents was it sports music
writing even here he's
trying not to stand out.
He's never been the
object of ridicule or envy
and he never reveals his
strengths or weaknesses
to anyone which means
it's all been a deception
he's been hiding his talent and intellect.
He knew laying low would be the
best way to stay out of trouble.
My hope in coming here was
to find hobbies or interests.
Any clue in the slightest.
Hobbies?
I may have found one.
For some weird reason, he keeps a
bunch of jars in this drawer. You see?
If you ask me, this looks like
a collection of bonito flakes.
But what is with the numbers?
1983. Hmm.
Must be the year.
Pee-yew, they smell rancid. What are they?
Seems they're fingernail clippings.
Whose nails do you
think they are? Hold on.
Calm down.
They're not from his victims.
Those clippings are his own.
He kept meticulous notes on the subject.
Notes?
You mean those numbers on the jars?
You mean he's been collecting
these things since 1983?
1983?
That's 15 years of yuck!
There are details about every finger!
According to this, in 1983,
his right thumb grew a nail that
was 31 and a half centimeters long!
Wait a sec!
I'm pretty sure 1983 was the
year Reimi Sugimoto was murdered!
Yeah, and the records begin in that year.
He probably reached a
point where he couldn't
repress his murderous impulses any longer.
Whoa!
This is all the info he
collected about his toenails!
A boring office worker seems to
have a very interesting hobby.
Look.
This is a form of divination.
It's similar to ancient
Jewish merchants who once
observed sunspots to
predict economic prospects.
It appears Yoshikage
Kira is tying his nail
growth to his physical
and mental preparedness.
His preparedness to kill, that is.
Check out 1999!
By June of this year, they'd
already grown over 20 centimeters!
I knew he was crazy, but this is sick.
I agree with you, but this
won't help us track him down.
There might be something else we can use.
What the hell, Jotaro?
You think someone's skulking
around the house under our noses?
Seems that way.
Josuke, stay on guard.
Could he have been maybe
working with a partner?
No way.
He's too cautious for that.
More people means more risk for capture.
A partner could just rat him out.
He wouldn't even consider it.
Is that...
Jotaro, quickly, look at the camera.
No doubt about it.
That's Kira's father.
He's behind us, just sitting
in the corner. Where'd he go?
That's really freaky.
We're in a shitload of trouble.
Are we actually dealing with a ghost?
Yeah, considering Raimi's situation,
it's entirely possible that his
father is stuck in some kind
of spiritual limbo between the
land of the living and the dead.
Look at his expression.
It seems like he wants
us to make a quick exit.
Hey, are you trying to give us the
willies with your spooky ghost energy?
This sucks, but we can't leave with
all this paranormal shit going on.
Answer the damn phone, slacker!
Can't you hear me calling?
You think my face is saying take a hike?
Well, you couldn't be more wrong!
You were looking at the face of a man who
will never allow you to
leave this house alive!
I'll kill you for going
after my son! Oh, fart!
Do you know about all the
crimes your son has committed?
Hey, you guys, what's with
all the racket in here?
Is something wrong?
Where the hell are you hiding?
Show yourself your geriatric ghost.
There's a ghost
Josuke, I don't think he's hiding at all.
Kira's father has been in the room
the entire time watching us you see.
When the hell did he he's able
to move around in the picture?
So it stands to reason he made
the call from in there and
he threw the phone at you from
inside the picture as well.
I'll kill you!
If you dare go after my dearest son,
I'll murder you!
Hey, Josuke!
Even if we can't physically
fight a ghost, our stance can!
On the day we met Reimi, Rohan sensei
used Tevin's door to read her memories!
Good to know!
How do you like this?
What?
Damage!
Damage inflicted on the
photograph backfires to us!
Fix it now, Josuke, or
we'll be ripped to shreds!
Thank goodness, you
guys are back to normal!
Those powers!
Yes, it's all making sense!
You whelps have special
abilities, like my son's!
Okuyasu!
It's time for you to do your thing!
You have to hurry up and use the hand to
cut this crusty old man out of the picture!
Gotcha!
You just leave everything
to me, Chillscape!
Okuyasu!
What the hell happened?
How'd I run straight into the window?
That's so weird!
What the heck?
Do you guys see my hands?
They're over there!
There's something stopping me from
coming into the room with you!
Huh?
What in the hell?
I don't know how, but there's an invisible
wall blocking anyone from entering!
And I don't think I can break it! Shit!
I see you finally figured it out.
This photo is special.
The invisible wall that
you're so worked up
about is actually the
edge of this picture.
I'm a ghost who lives out
his days in a photograph.
I can control the space of
any picture in which I appear.
By using that camera, I trap a person's
spiritual energy within a photograph.
That's my power.
The room you're in is inside the picture.
Damaging the photo means damaging
the spiritual energy too,
which won't end well for you.
But that doesn't make a lick of sense!
How are we in the picture
if I'm looking right at it?
You're clearly not the brightest,
so I'll spill it out for you.
After I kill these two fools,
I'll ensnare you and the brat?
and shred you to pieces!
J-Jusuke! Mr. Jotaro!
Time to die!
Bastard!
Get us out of here right now!
Jotaro, why are you just standing around?
Your Star Platinum is super powerful,
so hurry up and do something!
Sorry, Josuke, but I'm gonna
have to throw in the towel.
Huh?
Stopping that old-timers
attacks is downright impossible.
Every bit of damage we throw at him
will only come right back to us.
Star Platinum could stop time,
but there's really no point.
It'd be a waste of energy.
I can't believe it.
What are you saying?
Have you completely lost your mind?
Die! Die! Die!
Your heads have got
some good spin to them.
Great, he's got a knife.
It's not working!
I can't touch it, Jotaro!
I've given up on stopping the geezer.
However...
If he's being honest, it can really
control any photograph he's in.
But maybe the best way to win is to take a
shot of him so he's in
the picture by himself.
What the...
You found a way to sidestep
my attack entirely! Dammit!
Why don't you give our
friend here a nice send-off
and make sure you add a
little bit of style to it?
It looks like you weren't so
big and bad after all fool!
I Underestimated you, but I
see you're seasoned fighters?
You've got lots of experience battling
opponents with special abilities like my son,
don't you?
Remember the old farts a ghost
he can get out of the picture
We need to make sure you
behave yourself and stay put.
There's something in this house
you really don't want us to find.
That's why you're attacking us
with so much fervor, isn't it?
Oh, I get it.
If you fold that crusty old prune in
half, there's no way he can get out.
Looks like we win this one.
Okuyasu and Koichi search this room.
Josuke and I have got this one.
I can't protect my son
if I'm trapped in here.
What am I going to do?
If it falls into their
hands, it's all over.
What could he be hiding
that's so important
he'd do all this to
keep us from finding it?
I don't have the foggiest clue,
but I'm not going to sweat it.
If the old man turns white as a
sheet, we should be good. Help me!
I can't breathe!
It's torture in here!
Can't I have a bit of air?
Just poke a couple of holes in the
tape and let me catch my breath!
What?
You seriously can't breathe in there?
He's pulling your leg, Koichi.
Don't fall for it.
He wants you to make an
opening so he can get away.
I know you don't trust me, but I
really am dying in here, I swear!
I don't know about this, Okuyasu.
I'm claustrophobic, so I sort of get
what the poor guy's going through.
Oh, quit your bitchin', geezer.
If you really need a breathing hole
that bad, I'm more than happy to help.
Here, how's that working out for ya?
I know it's a little tacky.
What do you think you're doing?
Damn it, get me out of here,
you wretched little punk!
Sounds like you caught your breath.
Those tacks ain't going nowhere, Gramps.
Tax, you say?
That must mean you stuck me to the post.
What a red-letter day.
You idiots don't realize it, but
those tacks are my ticket out of here.
I couldn't have planned it better myself.
Much obliged, suckers. So long!
Hey, you pruney old bastard!
What the hell was that sound just now?
What did you do?
Open your mouth, dammit!
I'm talking to you!
I think we might have messed up!
What if he really used
the tacks to escape?
Mr. Jojuro!
Kira's father got away!
This mess is only happening because of me!
I stuck some tacks in it
and he did something weird!
You've been duped, my blockhead friend!
That was a battle of wits and you lost!
You mean he was faking?
There's no way!
I mean, this is the bow and
arrow, but why is it here?
I just don't understand.
We already retrieved them from Otoishi.
I thought the Speedwagon
Foundation was guarding them.
What's going on?
Is this another set?
Hey, watch out!
Kira's father has escaped!
Damn it!
This is the very arrow that
brought forth Deadly Queen!
Whoever wields it holds all the power!
I'll never let you take it from me!
Use Reverb, Koichi!
Sick Act 1 on him! I can't!
He's already too far away!
Freaking great!
At least now we know what Kira's father
was trying to stop us from finding!
He was hiding another bow and arrow!
Dammit!
It's all my fault!
No, Okuyasu.
He simply outsmarted us.
That geezer's definitely Kira's father.
There's no mistaking it.
They're gonna fight to
survive at all costs.
Their unrelenting resolve is
what's getting the best of us.
As long as those chumps don't
get this arrow, we'll be fine.
And in the meantime, I'll use it to
make even more enemies for them to face.
The bow and arrow.
So it's true.
I had a feeling there
might be more than one set.
That would explain how Dio
and his henchmen were able to
pull together such a large
group of stand users so quickly.
They built an army of minions across the
globe using multiple
sets of bows and arrows.
Kira's father probably obtained
this set from Inyaba the Witch.
And we already know Okuyasu's
brother Keicho came into
possession of one at some point
before they arrived in Morioh.
Stand users really do seem
to be drawn to each other.
Oh Yoshikage, where are you?
Even as a little boy, you couldn't
repress your urges to kill women.
But if that's what makes you happy,
I'll support and protect you.
That's my duty as a parent.
So, as you're my one and only
son, I'll do all I can for you.
I can't say I've ever seen
this side of you before.
I mean, since when do you know
your way around a kitchen?
It's not some kind of prank, is it?
There's two plates here,
so I assume one's mine.
You can't possibly think I'd eat
something you slopped together.
That's insane.
Seriously?
Do you really think now is the
best time to cut your nails?
Besides, you cut them
last night, didn't you?
They sure grow fast.
Holy shit!
This is actually delicious!
To be
continued...
I'm going to have to tell
you to leave it open!
Oh my goodness, what's
the matter, sweetie?
Why are you getting so worked up?
I guess cats aren't the
biggest fans of water.
My apologies.
I wasn't thinking and acted carelessly.
Sorry, it won't happen again.
There's definitely something
strange going on with him.
First he starts cooking for
me out of the blue and now
he's using an actual blade
instead of his electric razor.
Blades always give him razor burn.
Listen, pal, you still haven't
paid last month's rent.
You cheapskate.
Now you owe for this month.
So?
We'll fork over the yen,
not leave until I'm paid!
Rent?
You are the man.
Go and get the money from the
safe before he kicks us out.
Ride the safe.
Get a move on.
What are you waiting for?
You have the combination.
What are you doing?
Get back up here!
Thank you for taking the
time to drop by this morning.
But I appear to be running a
bit short on cash at the moment.
I'm sure you understand.
Huh?
Oh, that hair gel must be
seeping into your noggin?
I should have known you young deadbeats!
Wouldn't be able to
afford my gorgeous home.
That's what I get for doing
business with schmucks!
Learn to live within your means.
You'll get your money!
No, I think you misunderstood me earlier.
I said I was short on cash.
but I meant that I only
had a little over $500,000.
I'll only be able to pay for this month,
last month, and for the next
couple of months in advance.
Will that suffice for now?
Yes, that'll do nicely.
Thanks so much.
Have a good one.
Until next time.
What was that?
I don't know how, but you
must have stolen that money.
There's no point trying
to say that you didn't.
You stole it from the
landlord's bag, didn't you?
If anyone else was in this situation,
they'd be horrified that their
partner could do such a thing.
But his gusto.
The way he stole the money
and lied about it so easily.
I've been with him for so many years, but
he's never made me feel like this before.
It's exhilarating!
It's like I'm falling in love
with him for the first time.
Anytime I need to see your
face, it has closed my eyes.
And I am taking two bits
for your crystal mind!
A magenta feeling, take a
shelter in the face of my spine.
Like a Chaka cherry cola.
I don't need to try to explain?
I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again?
I'ma move so slightly.
To the arms and the lips.
And the face.
Of the humic.
And the ball.
That I need to.
I want to.
Come and stand.
A little bit closer.
Breathe in.
And get a bit higher.
You'll never know. What hit you.
When I get to you.
Oh I want you.
I don't know.
If I need you.
Oh I want you.
If I need help.
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
Ooh, I'm trying to find you.